(this.webpackJsonptransformersquiz=this.webpackJsonptransformersquiz||[]).push([[0],{13:function(e,t,s){},14:function(e,t,s){"use strict";s.r(t);var n=s(2),r=s(3),a=s(7),o=s(5),i=s(0),c=s.n(i),u=s(4),l=s.n(u),m=(s(13),[{question:"What year did the Transformers live action movie release?",answers:["2010","2008","2005","2007"],correct:"2007",questionId:"099099"},{question:"Who has directed all the transformers live action films?",answers:["Michael Bay","Martin Scorsese","Steven Spielberg","Quentin Tarantino"],correct:"Michael Bay",questionId:"183452"},{question:"What did Optimus Prime transform into?",answers:["18 Wheeler","Gun","Bus","Plane"],correct:"18 Wheeler",questionId:"267908"},{question:"Who was the leader of the Autobots?",answers:["Frenzy","Megatron","Optimus Prime","Starscream"],correct:"Optimus Prime",questionId:"333247"},{question:"What R&B singer played a role in the Transformers live action film?",answers:["Trey Songs","Tyrese Gibson","Chris Brown","Prince"],correct:"Tyrese Gibson",questionId:"496293"},{question:"How many Transformers movies have been made since the year 2011?",answers:["1","4","3","2"],correct:"3",questionId:"588909"},{question:"Who was the leader of the Decepticons?",answers:["Megatron","Bumblebee","Starscream","Bonecrusher"],correct:"Megatron",questionId:"648452"},{question:"What kind of Transformers car did the teenage boy own?",answers:["Charger","Corvette","Mustang","Camaro"],correct:"Camaro",questionId:"786649"},{question:"What was the name of the Transformers home planet?",answers:["Mars","Suntronics","Cybertron","Trans Earth"],correct:"Cybertron",questionId:"839754"},{question:"Who was the teenage boy that was friends with the Autobots?",answers:["Phillip","Tron","Sam","Tim"],correct:"Sam",questionId:"98390"},{question:"What was the Transformers cartoon called in Japan?",answers:["Fight! Super Robot Life Form Transformers","Robots from space","Warcraft Force Changers","Transform"],correct:"Fight! Super Robot Life Form Transformers",questionId:"1071006"},{question:"What is the name of Sam's dog?",answers:["Rex","Riley","Mojo","Buster"],correct:"Mojo",questionId:"1174154"},{question:"Who did Sentinel Prime kill in Tranformers: Dark Of The Moon?",answers:["Bumblebee","Ironhide","Starscream","Shockwave"],correct:"Ironhide",questionId:"1226535"},{question:"Who's gun did Optimus Prime use to kill Sentinel Prime?",answers:["Soundwave"," Megatron","Shockwave","Starscream"],correct:"Megatron",questionId:"1310938"},{question:"What is Mark Wahlberg's character called?",answers:["Cade Yeager","Samuel James Witwicky","Lucas","Joshua"],correct:"Cade Yeager",questionId:"1436873"},{question:"What band plays the theme song for Transformers: Age of Extinction?",answers:["Red Hot Chilli Peppers","Pink Floyd","AC/DC","Imagine Dragons"],correct:"Imagine Dragons",questionId:"1515110"},{question:"What college does Sam go to?",answers:["Princeton University","UCLA","Columbia University","Duke University"],correct:"Princeton University",questionId:"1642728"},{question:"Who died from Lockdown's grenade? ",answers:["Cade","Tessa","Lucas","Joshua"],correct:"Lucas",questionId:"1747256"},{question:"What word represents the letter 'T' in the NATO phonetic alphabet?",answers:["Tango","Target","Taxi","Turkey"],correct:"Tango",questionId:"1822532"},{question:"What is Sam's Ebay username called out by Barricade?",answers:["Actionman22","Icefox","Ladiesman217","Lastman4"],correct:"LadiesMan217",questionID:"195075"}]),h=function(){var e=arguments.length>0&&void 0!==arguments[0]?arguments[0]:5;return Promise.resolve(m.sort((function(){return.5-Math.random()})).slice(0,e))},d=s(6),f=function(e){var t=e.question,s=e.options,n=e.selected,r=Object(i.useState)(s),a=Object(d.a)(r,2),o=a[0],u=a[1];return c.a.createElement("div",{className:"questionBox"},c.a.createElement("div",{className:"question"},t),o.map((function(e,t){return c.a.createElement("button",{key:t,className:"answerBtn",onClick:function(){u([e]),n(e)}},e)})))},q=function(e){var t=e.score,s=e.playAgain;return c.a.createElement("div",{className:"score-board"},c.a.createElement("div",{className:"score"},"You scored ",t," / 5 correct answers!"),c.a.createElement("button",{className:"playBtn",onClick:s},"Play again!"))},p=function(e){Object(a.a)(s,e);var t=Object(o.a)(s);function s(){var e;Object(n.a)(this,s);for(var r=arguments.length,a=new Array(r),o=0;o<r;o++)a[o]=arguments[o];return(e=t.call.apply(t,[this].concat(a))).state={questionBank:[],score:0,responses:0},e.getQuestions=function(){h().then((function(t){e.setState({questionBank:t})}))},e.computeAnswer=function(t,s){t===s&&e.setState({score:e.state.score+1}),e.setState({responses:e.state.responses<5?e.state.responses+1:5})},e.playAgain=function(){e.getQuestions(),e.setState({score:0,responses:0})},e}return Object(r.a)(s,[{key:"componentDidMount",value:function(){this.getQuestions()}},{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this;return c.a.createElement("div",{className:"Container"},c.a.createElement("div",{className:"title"},"Transformers Quiz"),this.state.questionBank.length>0&&this.state.responses<5&&this.state.questionBank.map((function(t){var s=t.question,n=t.answers,r=t.correct,a=t.questionId;return c.a.createElement(f,{question:s,options:n,key:a,selected:function(t){return e.computeAnswer(t,r)}})})),5===this.state.responses?c.a.createElement(q,{score:this.state.score,playAgain:this.playAgain}):null)}}]),s}(i.Component);l.a.render(c.a.createElement(p,null),document.getElementById("root"))},8:function(e,t,s){e.exports=s(14)}},[[8,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.e76ff44f.chunk.js.map